time for tonight's hashtag
Wars all right the state uh of course
one of the greatest sketch comedy shows
it was on MTV in the 1990s we were there
around the same time almost back in the
1900s oh back in the 1990s kids that was
before we had
[Laughter]
machines well in honor of your guys'
show we've decided to make our hashtag
tonight sad te TV shows all right it's
basically making a TV show title sad so
instances would be um all in the death
in the family or slaved by the Bell or
Reno 911 would be another version of
that so I'm going to put 60 seconds on
the clock starting now and go show
Walter the wheel of Misfortune yes
points G Kenny how I met the guy I think
might be your father oh very sad tale
yes points Mike black the brave ay Bunch
why is that sad CU they' got AIDS in the
middle of the I got you okay yes that
would be very sad that would be very sad
points yes I you know what I have to
give him points yes shower Downer Abby
yes points car Kenny the big gang bang
the yes oh not so sad not so sad it is
if it's happening to you okay points
okay points yes Mike flag Full House of
children orphaned by the earthquake in
Haiti punch yes very sad Kenny America's
Got
Crabs that is a true statement and also
a great points title yes Mike black Dora
the by curious Explorer yes
points yes Mike Showalter Chernobyl
5 Points Gary Law and Order Special
Olympics
unit points flag The Tonight Show with
Conan O'Brien oh yeah points that was a
sad thing that happened yes
definitely